Quicksilver Highway is a horror, thriller, tv
movie film directed by Mick Garris.
Aaron Quicksilver is a mysterious storyteller whose listeners invariably
end up as the subjects of his gruesome, grisly tales.
He tells a new bride stranded on a desert highway a horrifying account of a set of carnivorous toy teeth, then
entrains a pickpocket with the spine chilling story of an army of murderous, disembodied hands.
Aaron Quicksilver, played by Christopher Lloyd.
Charlie / Dr. Charles George, played by Matt Frewer.
Kerry Parker / Bill Hogan, played by Raphael Sbarge.
Olivia Harmon Parker / Lita Hogan, played by Missy Crider.
Bryan Adams, played by Silas Weir Mitchell.
Len, played by Bill Nunn.
Quicksilver Highway is a 1997 made for television comedy
horror anthology film directed by Mick Garris.
It is based on Clive Barker's 1985 short story "The Body Politic"
and Stephen King's 1992 short story "Chattery Teeth".
The film was originally shown on the Fox Network on 13 May
1997, before being released on home media.
The tone is dark and intense.